[
                {
                "Question":"1.How do I add scrolling text to my page?",
                "optionA":"strong",
                "optionB":"Marquee",
                "optionC":"blockquote",
                "optionD":"em",
                "answer":"2",
                "amount":"1,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["1","3"],
                "peoplePoll":[10,65,15,10]
                },
               {
                "Question":"2.Which tag defines the caption for a fieldset element?",
                "optionA":"optgroup",
                "optionB":"caption",
                "optionC":"legend",
                "optionD":"label",
                "answer":"3",
                "amount":"2,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["1","4"],
                "peoplePoll":[30,10,45,15]
                },

              {
                "Question":"3.Which HTML tag is used to define a internal style sheet?",
                "optionA":"<CSS>",
                "optionB":"<Script>",
                "optionC":"<style>",
                "optionD":"<link>",
                "answer":"3",
                "amount":"3,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["2","4"],
                "peoplePoll":[10,30,50,10]
                },

              {
                "Question":"4.Which is the correct CSS syntax?",
                "optionA":"body{color: black}",
                "optionB":"body: color=black",
                "optionC":"{body ;color: black}",
                "optionD":"{body: color=black(body}",
                "answer":"1",
                "amount":"4,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["2","3"],
                "peoplePoll":[40,25,5,30]
                },
                
              {
                "Question":"5.How do you write \"Hello World\" in an alertbox?",
                "optionA":"alertbox(\"hello world\")",
                "optionB":"alert(\"Hello World\")",
                "optionC":"alertbox=\"Hello World\"",
                "optionD":"msgbox(\"hello World\")",
                "answer":"2",
                "amount":"5,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["1","3"],
                "peoplePoll":[10,50,20,10]
                },

              {
                "Question":"6.How can you add an comment in a javascript?",
                "optionA":"//This is a comment",
                "optionB":"<!- - This is a comment-- >",
                "optionC":"This is a comment",
                "optionD":"/This is a comment",
                "answer":"1",
                "amount":"6,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["3","4"],
                "peoplePoll":[55,25,10,10]
                },

                {
                "Question":"7.What does CSS stands for?",
                "optionA":"Computer style sheet",
                "optionB":"Colorful style sheet",
                "optionC":"Creative style sheet",
                "optionD":"Cascading style sheet",
                "answer":"4",
                "amount":"7,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["1","2"],
                "peoplePoll":[10,20,30,40]
                },
              {
                "Question":"8.Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
                "optionA":"font",
                "optionB":"style",
                "optionC":"styles",
                "optionD":"class",
                "answer":"2",
                "amount":"8,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["1","4"],
                "peoplePoll":[5,45,30,20]
                },

              {
                "Question":"9.Which CSS property controls the text size?",
                "optionA":"font-size",
                "optionB":"text-style",
                "optionC":"font-style",
                "optionD":"text-size",
                "answer":"1",
                "amount":"9,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["3","4"],
                "peoplePoll":[50,30,10,10]
                },
                {
                "Question":"10.Which of the following is not new element of HTML5?",
                "optionA":"<article>",
                "optionB":"<aside>",
                "optionC":"<command>",
                "optionD":"<big>",
                "answer":"4",
                "amount":"10,00,000",
                "fiftyFifty":["1","2"],
                "peoplePoll":[15,5,30,50]
                }
        ]
